Updated: September 2024

# Lorenzo Godi

 Padova, Italy
 Iorenzo.godi.work@protonmail.com
 in lorenzogodi
 ♠ LorenzoGodi

#### **About Me**

I am a computer scientist and an astronomy student. My pursuit in life has always been knowledge. I was just six years old when I was captivated in front of the screen by a documentary about black holes. I appreciate and need to constantly deepen my understanding of the world. Computer sciences have always been my strong suit since high school. I enjoy designing software and programming. You will find in me an highly motivated person, willing to learn and face challenges and capable of working independently. I also enjoy collaborating in a team environment and exchanging ideas. I would love to dedicate myself to a stimulating project, growing my abilities and passion.

#### Education

#### **University of Padova**

2021 - present

Bachelor's Degree in Astronomy (attending)

**University of Trento** 

2018 - 2021

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Sciences

o **Final grade:** 110 cum laude / 110

 Internship and final exam: "Data Analysis in the climate domain on HPC clusters using the parallel data analytics framework Dask"

## Technical School ITT "Eugenio Barsanti"

2013 - 2018

Diploma in Informatics and Telecommunications - Specialisation: Informatics

o **Final grade:** 100 / 100

# **Experience**

### **Apprenticeship - IT and Telematics Systems Officer**

Venezia, Italy Nov 2023 – present

Accenture Italia

- o Windows System Administrator at Public Administration Offices.
- o PowerShell and Python scripting.
- o Deployment of applications on Windows Server.
- o Managed Windows Server services, including Active Directory, DFS, WSUS, and DNS.
- o Configuring monitoring services such as Dynatrace, Zabbix

## Online Technical Support Operator

Trento, Italy May 2020 – May 2021

University of Trento

- o Provided support to academic departments for conducting virtual graduation sessions.
- o Managed and organised Zoom meetings, offering technical assistance.

## **Volunteering**

#### IT Tutor for adults

Technical School ITT "Eugenio Barsanti"

- o Conducted basic IT courses for adults on using computers, smartphones, and the internet.
- Developed instructional guides and prepared lesson materials.

## **Technologies**

Languages: Python (Numpy, Xarray, Matplotlib), SQL, PowerShell, C#, JAVA, SML, F#

Tools: Jupyter Lab, Git, LateX

Familiar with: .NET, Docker, C++, JavaScript, Typescript, Bash